# **BRUNO SALA**

Full Stack Software Engineer PHP, Node.js oriented stacks brunosala.com Hello! My name is Daniel Bruno Sala, I'm a self-starting Full Stack Software Engineer based out of Chicago, IL. I've worked with a diverse array of clients from various countries on projects that range from simple website development to enterprise-scale application engineering. My goal is to deliver high quality, bold products to my clients all while having a bit of fun.

I attribute my success as a software engineer to having strong algorithm development and technical communication skills. Being able to pass on not only the solution but the "recipe" to the solution offers much more than just a deliverable.

## CONTACT

Email: connect@brunosala.com Phone: +1 (513) 668-7678 Location: Greater Chicago Area

# FRONT END

SCSS
CSS in JS, React-JSS
Tailwind CSS
JavaScript, TypeScript
Angular 2+, RxJS
React, Redux
Babel
NX, Create React App

# **BACK END**

PHP Laravel, Symfony mySQL/MariaDB PostgreSQL WordPress, Drupal, Joomla

Node.js, Express Gatsby, Next.js GraphQL MongoDB

#### **DEVOPS**

Apache, NGINX Docker Kubernetes AWS Jenkins, Terraform

#### **EDUCATION**

Associate's Degree in Management and Information Systems

## **REFERENCES**

Corey Simpson - COO ILTA corey@iltanet.org

Phillip Bergner - CTO All Digital Solutions phil@alldigitalsolutions.com

#### CONNECT

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/brunosala

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **Lead Full Stack Engineer**

Aug 2020 - Present

Allbound

Core contributor to new product features, legacy code management and upcycling, and project management.

- ☐ Interviewing and onboarding of new engineers
- Majority code review contributor
- Core contributor to internal tooling and architecture projects designed to dramatically modernize the platform
  - React 10.x -> React 16.x, Redux state management and module based methodology
  - Codeigniter -> Laravel, MongoDB and GraphQL drivers
  - MongoDB implementation
- Orchestrated aforementioned projects: scheduled meetings with stakeholders, designed workbooks, decision documents, and telephone logs

# **Front End Developer**

Oct 2018 - April 2020

International Legal Technology Association

Lead the development of new websites, landing pages, and mobile applications utilizing Angular 2+ and assisted in a large scale data migration into Salesforce.

- ☐ Utilized Angular 2+, Karma, Apache Cordova, and Force.js to build, test, and deploy to browser. Android, and iOS
- Assisted in the migration of 30+ years worth of customer data into Salesforce CRM

# Front End Developer

April 2017 - April 2018

All Digital Solutions

Created unique digital marketing solutions, websites, and automation utilities that were distributed to 50+ clients.

- Developed multiple hybrid mobile applications using Angular and Apache Cordova with authorization, networking and live notification systems
- ☐ Built a headless CMS solution to allow clients to remotely manage digital signage

## **Full Stack Developer**

April 2018 - Oct 2018

The Creative Group

June 2016 - April 2017

Nov 2014 - June 2016

Interviewed clients, created project management documentation, and led development on LAMP and JavaScript projects.

# Full Stack Developer

Freelance - Full Time

Utilized multiple client aggregation tools to make a living building websites and implementing CMS tools, and managing e-commerce platforms.